A Guide to the Records of William James McKeefery, Vice President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1969-1973
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Records of William James McKeefery, Vice President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1969-1973
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 4/2
26 cu. ft.; 26 boxes
McKeefery, William James, 1918-
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Records of William James McKeefery, Vice President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute were transferred to Special Collections.
Biographical Note
Dr. McKeefery was educated at University of Pennsylvania (B.S., Electrical Engineering, 1941), Princeton Theological Seminary (B.D.,Theology, 1945), and Columbia University (Ph.D., Philosophy, 1949). Before assuming his post at Virginia Tech, he was Dean of Academic Affairs, Southern Illinois University, Carbondale (1961-1969); Vice President, Washburn University, Topeka Kansas (11958-1961); Dean of the Faculty (1950-1958) and Assistant Professor (1948-1949), Alma College, Alma, Michigan. He served as the second Executive Vice President of Virginia Polytechnic Institite from 1969 to 1973. Author of Parameters of Learning: Perspectives in Higher Education (Southern Illinois University Press, 1970), Curriculum Study: Master Plan for Higher Education, State of Illinois (1964), and A Critical Analysis of Psychological Studies of Religious Phenomena (Eagle Press, 1950).
Scope and Content
In 1968 the post of Executive Vice President was established. William James McKeefery was the second Executive Vice President, succeeding Warren Brandt. This collection contains the correspondence and other official files of McKeefery during his tenure as Executive Vice-President. There is material dealing with the College of Agriculture, College of Arts and Sciences, College of Business, College of Education, College of Engineering, Home Economics, Committee to Study Revision of University Council, International Programs, new degree programs, Learning Resources Center, Inter-American Institute of Ecology, Education Task Force, Phi Beta Kappa, Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, Squires Student Center, State Council of Higher Education in Virginia, Student Government Association, Urban Transport Consortium, and University Council. There is also a large amount of correspondence with T. Marshall Hahn.
Arrangement
The collection is in its original order.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Materials
For a description of the records of McKeefery's predecessor, Warren Brandt, see Record Group 3 - Office of the Vice President: http://spec.lib.vt.edu/archives/guide/rg03.htm.
For records of McKeefery's successor, see the finding aid for the Records of William E. Lavery.
For additional records from other university offices, see the University Archives website: http://spec.lib.vt.edu/archives/.
Index Terms
Names:
McKeefery, William James, 1918-
Subjects:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Local Subjects
Faculty; University Archives
Contents List
- Administration Planning Session. (Box-folder 1-1)
- Admissions - Lacy. (Box-folder 1-2)
- Agriculture, College of. (Box-folder 1-3)
- Ambulance Service. (Box-folder 1-4)
- American Security Council. (Box-folder 1-5)
- Animal Science Department. (Box-folder 1-6)
- Arts and Sciences. (Box-folder 1-7)
- Athletic Association. (Box-folder 1-8)
- Back-Up Plans. (Box-folder 1-9)
- Bell, Wilson B., Development. (Box-folder 1-10)
- Board of Visitors. (Box-folder 1-11)
- Budget 1. (Box-folder 1-12)
- Budget 2. (Box-folder 1-13)
- Budget Preparation 1. (Box-folder 1-14)
- Budget Preparation 2, Instruction Regular Session. (Box-folder 1-15)
- Budget Preparation 3, Instruction Summer Session. (Box-folder 1-16)
- Budget Preparation 4, Organized Activities. (Box-folder 1-17)
- Budget Preparation 5, Library. (Box-folder 1-18)
- Building Committee 1. (Box-folder 1-19)
- Building Committee 2. (Box-folder 1-20)
- Building Committee 3. (Box-folder 1-21)
- Building Committee 4. (Box-folder 1-22)
- Building Committee 5. (Box-folder 1-23)
- Burchard, Charles - Architecture. (Box-folder 1-24)
- Business Administration. (Box-folder 1-25)
- Campus Ministries. (Box-folder 1-26)
- Cassell, Stuart K. (Box-folder 1-27)
- Catalog Committee. (Box-folder 1-28)
- College of Architecture - Direction for the seventies. (Box-folder 1-29)
- College of Architecture - Master of Arch. Degree Proposal. (Box-folder 1-30)
- Commencement. (Box-folder 1-31)
- Community College. (Box-folder 1-32)
- Computer - Literature, Articles, Reprints. (Box-folder 1-33)
- Computer Committee. (Box-folder 1-34)
- Computer Committee 1. (Box-folder 1-35)
- Computer Committee 2. (Box-folder 1-36)
- Computer Committee 3. (Box-folder 1-37)
- Computing Equipment Acquisition. (Box-folder 1-38)
- Computing Center Log. (Box-folder 1-39)
- Constitution. (Box-folder 1-40)
- Consulting. (Box-folder 1-41)
- Continuing Education Center. (Box-folder 1-42)
- Cooperative Education. (Box-folder 1-43)
- Council of Deans Meeting. (Box-folder 1-44)
- Carbons from Hahn 1. (Box-folder 2-45)
- Carbons from Hahn 2. (Box-folder 2-46)
- Carbons from Hahn 3. (Box-folder 2-47)
- Carbons from Hahn 4. (Box-folder 2-48)
- Carbons from Hahn 5. (Box-folder 2-49)
- Carbons from Hahn 6. (Box-folder 2-50)
- Carbons from Hahn 7. (Box-folder 2-51)
- Carbons from Hahn 8. (Box-folder 2-52)
- Carbons from Hahn 9. (Box-folder 2-53)
- Carbons from Hahn 10. (Box-folder 2-54)
- Carbons from Hahn 11. (Box-folder 2-55)
- Carbons from Hahn 12. (Box-folder 2-56)
- Carbons from Hahn 13. (Box-folder 2-57)
- Carbons from Hahn 14. (Box-folder 2-58)
- Dean Brown. (Box-folder 2-59)
- Dean Harder. (Box-folder 2-60)
- Dean J.W. - VP Students 1. (Box-folder 2-61)
- Dean J.W. - VP Students 2. (Box-folder 2-62)
- Dean J.W. - VP Students 3. (Box-folder 2-63)
- Dean J.W. - VP Students 4. (Box-folder 2-64)
- Deans Discipline. (Box-folder 2-65)
- Dedications. (Box-folder 2-66)
- Dormitory and Dining Halls. (Box-folder 2-67)
- Economics Department. (Box-folder 2-68)
- EDUCOM. (Box-folder 2-69)
- Engineering, College of - 1. (Box-folder 2-70)
- Engineering, College of - 2. (Box-folder 2-71)
- Exchange Visitor Program DSP-66. (Box-folder 2-72)
- Extension Division 1. (Box-folder 2-73)
- Extension Division 2. (Box-folder 2-74)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 2-75)
- Financial Aid. (Box-folder 2-76)
- Forestry and Wildlife. (Box-folder 2-77)
- Foundation. (Box-folder 2-78)
- General Electric. (Box-folder 2-79)
- Geology Department. (Box-folder 2-80)
- Glee Club. (Box-folder 2-81)
- Governors Day. (Box-folder 2-82)
- Graduate Committee Minutes. (Box-folder 2-83)
- Graduate School 1. (Box-folder 2-84)
- Graduate School 2. (Box-folder 2-85)
- Graduate Studies - Reston 1. (Box-folder 2-86)
- Graduate Studies - Reston 2. (Box-folder 2-87)
- Graduate Studies - Reston 3. (Box-folder 2-88)
- Graduate Studies - Reston 4. (Box-folder 2-89)
- Grant Proposals. (Box-folder 2-90)
- T. Marshall Hahn Jr. - 1. (Box-folder 2-91)
- T. Marshall Hahn Jr. - 2. (Box-folder 2-92)
- Harper, Laura Jane - HEC. (Box-folder 2-93)
- Harper, George. (Box-folder 2-94)
- History Department. (Box-folder 2-95)
- Honor Court. (Box-folder 2-96)
- Housing: Off-Campus. (Box-folder 2-97)
- Industrial Engineering. (Box-folder 3-98)
- Industry Center. (Box-folder 3-99)
- Information Services. (Box-folder 3-100)
- Interface Committee 1. (Box-folder 3-101)
- Interface Committee 2. (Box-folder 3-102)
- Interface Committee 3. (Box-folder 3-103)
- International Program Education. (Box-folder 3-104)
- Institutional Research. (Box-folder 3-105)
- Judicial Committee. (Box-folder 3-106)
- Dr. W.E. Lavery 1. (Box-folder 3-107)
- Dr. W.E. Lavery 2. (Box-folder 3-108)
- Law Enforcement. (Box-folder 3-109)
- Library. (Box-folder 3-110)
- Library Committee. (Box-folder 3-111)
- Malpaos, Leslie F. - 1. (Box-folder 3-112)
- Malpaos, Leslie F. - 2. (Box-folder 3-113)
- Malpaos, Leslie F. - 3. (Box-folder 3-114)
- Malpaos, Leslie F. - 4. (Box-folder 3-115)
- Malpaos, Leslie F. - 5. (Box-folder 3-116)
- Martin, James E. - Dean. (Box-folder 3-117)
- Mathematics Department. (Box-folder 3-118.)
- Miscellaneous Letters. (Box-folder 3-119)
- Miscellaneous Reports (Figures). (Box-folder 3-120)
- Mining Engineering. (Box-folder 3-121)
- Mitchell, H.H. - Dean. (Box-folder 3-122)
- James Montgomery. (Box-folder 3-123)
- Name Change. (Box-folder 3-124)
- National Association State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC). (Box-folder 3-125)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 3-126)
- Operation Breakthrough 1. (Box-folder 3-127)
- Operation Breakthrough 2. (Box-folder 3-128)
- Orientation Committee 1. (Box-folder 3-129)
- Orientation Committee 2. (Box-folder 3-130)
- Pass-Fail Letters. (Box-folder 3-131)
- Payne, Alfred C. (Box-folder 3-132)
- Personal 1. (Box-folder 3-133)
- Personal 2. (Box-folder 3-134)
- Personal 3. (Box-folder 3-135)
- Personal 4. (Box-folder 3-136)
- Personal 5. (Box-folder 3-137)
- Personnel. (Box-folder 3-138)
- Physics Department. (Box-folder 3-139)
- Placement. (Box-folder 3-140)
- Political Science. (Box-folder 3-141)
- Poultry Science Department. (Box-folder 3-142)
- Promotions of Faculty. (Box-folder 3-143)
- Prospective Personnel. (Box-folder 3-144)
- Prospective Personnel - Reston 1. (Box-folder 3-145)
- Prospective Personnel - Reston 2. (Box-folder 3-146)
- Prospective Personnel - Reston 3. (Box-folder 3-147)
- Quality Credit Averages. (Box-folder 3-148)
- Radio Station (Proposed). (Box-folder 3-149)
- Registrar - Keller. (Box-folder 3-150)
- Requisitions - Expense And Travel. (Box-folder 3-151)
- Research Division 1. (Box-folder 3-152)
- Research Division 2. (Box-folder 3-153)
- Salary Information. (Box-folder 3-154)
- Schedules. (Box-folder 3-155)
- South Boston - MBA - Westinghouse Company. (Box-folder 3-156)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities. (Box-folder 3-157)
- Speaking Engagements. (Box-folder 3-158)
- Staff Meetings. (Box-folder 3-159)
- State Council Of Higher Education. (Box-folder 3-160)
- State Technical Services. (Box-folder 4-161)
- Statement - Expenditures and Balances. (Box-folder 4-162)
- Statistics Department. (Box-folder 4-163)
- Student Appeals. (Box-folder 4-164)
- Students 1. (Box-folder 4-165)
- Students 2. (Box-folder 4-166)
- Student Activities Committee 1. (Box-folder 4-167)
- Student Activities Committee 2. (Box-folder 4-168)
- Student Forums Board. (Box-folder 4-169)
- Student Government - July 1969-December 1969. (Box-folder 4-170)
- Student Government - January 1969-June 1969. (Box-folder 4-171)
- Student Union. (Box-folder 4-172)
- Students' Letters. (Box-folder 4-173)
- Tech Festival. (Box-folder 4-174)
- Themis. (Box-folder 4-175)
- Commission Reports - Faculty, Undergraduate Affairs, Studies Research, and Graduate Studies. (Box-folder 4-176)
- Traffic Committee. (Box-folder 4-177)
- Themis Proposal - Mechanics of New Configurations in Plate, Shell, and Composite Structures. (Box-folder 4-178)
- Themis Proposal - Prediction of High-Speed Viscous flows by Numerical Methods. (Box-folder 4-179)
- Themis Proposal - Ceramic Particle Processing and Characterization. (Box-folder 4-180)
- University Council. (Box-folder 4-181)
- University Council 1. (Box-folder 4-182)
- University Council 2. (Box-folder 4-183)
- University Council 3. (Box-folder 4-184)
- University Council 4. (Box-folder 4-185)
- University Council 5. (Box-folder 4-186)
- University Council 6. (Box-folder 4-187)
- University Council 7. (Box-folder 4-188)
- Upward Bound. (Box-folder 4-189)
- Urban Transport Consortium. (Box-folder 4-190)
- Vandenberg, H.P.C. (Box-folder 5-191)
- V.A.R.C. (Box-folder 5-192)
- Veterinary Science. (Box-folder 5-193)
- Virginia Academy of Science. (Box-folder 5-194)
- Visiting Scholars - College and Departmental. (Box-folder 5-195)
- Visiting Scholars Brochures 1. (Box-folder 5-196)
- Visiting Scholars Brochures 2. (Box-folder 5-197)
- Visiting Scholar Honorarium. (Box-folder 5-198)
- Visiting Scholars - University. (Box-folder 5-199)
- William and Mary College. (Box-folder 5-200)
- Worcester, Wills G. - Dean. (Box-folder 5-201)
- Y.M.C.A. (Box-folder 5-202)
- Bio-Medical Engineering - Proposed Program. (Box-folder 5-203)
- Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association and College Retirement Equities Fund (TIAA-CREF). (Box-folder 5-204)
- University Council 1. (Box-folder 5-205)
- University Council 2. (Box-folder 5-206)
- University Council 3. (Box-folder 5-207)
- University Council 4. (Box-folder 5-208)
- University Council 5. (Box-folder 5-209)
- University Council 6. (Box-folder 5-210)
- Vandenberg, H.P.C. (Box-folder 5-211)
- V.A.R.C. 1. (Box-folder 5-212)
- V.A.R.C. 2. (Box-folder 5-213)
- Proposed Graduate School Sites - Reston, Va. (Box-folder 5-214)
- Accounts. (Box-folder 5-215)
- Accounting Department. (Box-folder 5-216)
- Program Developments. (Box-folder 5-217)
- Proposed Degree Programs 1. (Box-folder 5-218)
- Proposed Degree Programs 2. (Box-folder 5-219)
- Proposed Degree Programs 3. (Box-folder 5-220)
- Off-Campus Planning: November 2-3. (Box-folder 5-221)
- Administrators Conference: September 8-9. (Box-folder 5-222)
- Admissions - Dr. Lacy. (Box-folder 5-223)
- Agriculture, College of. (Box-folder 5-224)
- Virginia Tech Computing Center - Annual Reports. (Box-folder 5-225)
- Alumni Association. (Box-folder 6-226)
- Ambulance. (Box-folder 6-227)
- American Association Higher Education. (Box-folder 6-228)
- Animal Science Department. (Box-folder 6-229)
- American Association of University Professors (AAUP). (Box-folder 6-230)
- American Council on Education. (Box-folder 6-231)
- Anaerobe Laboratory (Manual). (Box-folder 6-232)
- Annual Physical Examination. (Box-folder 6-233)
- Appalachia. (Box-folder 6-234)
- Architecture, College of. (Box-folder 6-235)
- Arts and Sciences. (Box-folder 6-236)
- Proposed Degree Program. (Box-folder 6-237)
- Southern Humanities Conference. (Box-folder 6-238)
- Athletic Association. (Box-folder 6-239)
- Battelle Corporation. (Box-folder 6-240)
- Bell, Wilson B. - Development. (Box-folder 6-241)
- Blacksburg, Town. (Box-folder 6-242)
- Board of Visitors. (Box-folder 6-243\)
- Board of Visitors Orientation. (Box-folder 6-244)
- Budget. (Box-folder 6-245)
- Building Committee - Health and Physical Education/ (Box-folder 6-246)
- Building Committee - Library. (Box-folder 6-247)
- Building Committee - Classrooms and Administration Buildings. (Box-folder 6-248)
- Building Committee - July 30, 1971 - June 1970 (Box-folder 6-249)
- Building Committee - May 1970 - February 27, 1970. (Box-folder 6-250)
- Building Committee - February 10, 1970 - November 17, 1969. (Box-folder 6-251)
- Building Committee (General Information). (Box-folder 6-252)
- Building Committee - Dormitory. (Box-folder 6-253)
- Building Committee - Field House. (Box-folder 6-254)
- Buildings and Grounds. (Box-folder 6-255)
- Business Manager. (Box-folder 6-256)
- Burchard, Charles. (Box-folder 6-257)
- Business Administration. (Box-folder 6-258)
- Bussing. (Box-folder 6-259)
- Byrd, Harry F. (Box-folder 6-260)
- Cassell, Stuart K. (Box-folder 6-261)
- Centennial Plans. (Box-folder 6-262)
- Center for Environmental Studies. (Box-folder 6-263)
- Chemical Engineering Department. (Box-folder 6-264)
- Civilian Interdormitory Council. (Box-folder 6-265)
- Commencement. (Box-folder 6-266)
- Commission Reports. (Box-folder 6-267)
- Commission - Faculty Affairs. (Box-folder 6-268)
- Commission Research and Graduate Studies. (Box-folder 6-269)
- Commission - Undergraduate Studies. (Box-folder 6-270)
- Commission - Undergraduate Student Affairs. (Box-folder 6-271)
- Commission - Undergraduate Student Affairs. (Box-folder 6-272)
- Community Colleges. (Box-folder 6-273)
- Computer Committee - Executive Committee. (Box-folder 6-274)
- Computer Committee. (Box-folder 6-275)
- Computer Committee - General Information. (Box-folder 6-276)
- Computer Committee Minutes. (Box-folder 7-277)
- Computer Center Log. (Box-folder 7-278)
- Computer Center. (Box-folder 7-279)
- Consulting. (Box-folder 7-280)
- Consulting. (Box-folder 7-281)
- Consulting Education Center. (Box-folder 7-282)
- Cooperative Education. (Box-folder 7-283)
- Corps of Cadets. (Box-folder 7-284)
- Council Of Deans. (Box-folder 7-285)
- Counseling Center. (Box-folder 7-286)
- Cowgill Hall Occupation. (Box-folder 7-287)
- Dean of Discipline. (Box-folder 7-288)
- James W. Dean - Special Reports. (Box-folder 7-289)
- Deans and Departments - Chairmen. (Box-folder 7-290)
- James W. Dean - July 1. (Box-folder 7-291)
- James W. Dean - July 1. (Box-folder 7-292)
- Dean Brown. (Box-folder 7-293)
- James Dean - May 1 - June 30. (Box-folder 7-294)
- Dean, James W. (Box-folder 7-295)
- Dean, James W. (Box-folder 7-296)
- Dean Harder. (Box-folder 7-297)
- Decorating, Interior. (Box-folder 7-298)
- Disciplinary Panel, Recommendation. (Box-folder 7-299)
- Disruptive Activities. (Box-folder 7-300)
- Dormitory and Dining Halls (Box-folder 7-301)
- Ecological Studies. (Box-folder 7-302)
- Economics Department. (Box-folder 8-303)
- Education. (Box-folder 8-304)
- Educational Foundation. (Box-folder 8-305)
- Education And Gifts. (Box-folder 8-306)
- Report to be Used of Educational Television. (Box-folder 8-307)
- Educational Television. (Box-folder 8-308)
- Edocom. (Box-folder 8-309)
- Engineering, College of. (Box-folder 8-310)
- Engineering, College of. (Box-folder 8-311)
- Engineering, College of. (Box-folder 8-312)
- Metals and Ceramic Engineering. (Box-folder 8-313)
- Exchange Visitor Program Previously Reported. (Box-folder 8-314)
- Extension Division. (Box-folder 8-315)
- Exchange Visitor Program Robertson, Robert Teller. (Box-folder 8-316)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 8-317)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 8-318)
- Foreign Language Department. (Box-folder 8-319)
- Forestry and Wildlife. (Box-folder 8-320)
- 4-H Club. (Box-folder 8-321)
- Fraternities & Sororities. (Box-folder 8-322)
- General Computing Corp. (Box-folder 8-323)
- Geology Department. (Box-folder 8-324)
- Glee Club. (Box-folder 8-325)
- Governor's Day. (Box-folder 8-326)
- Governor's Study. (Box-folder 8-327)
- Grade Summaries. (Box-folder 8-328)
- Graduate School. (Box-folder 8-329)
- Graduate Studies - Reston. (Box-folder 8-330)
- Graduate Committee. (Box-folder 8-331)
- Grants and Gifts. (Box-folder 8-332)
- TMH (T. Marshall Hahn)- December. (Box-folder 8-333)
- Dr. Hahn - November 1970. (Box-folder 8-334)
- TMH - October 1970. (Box-folder 8-335)
- TMH - September 1970. (Box-folder 8-336)
- TMH - August 1970. (Box-folder 9-337)
- TMH - July 1970. (Box-folder 9-338)
- TMH - June 1970. (Box-folder 9-339)
- TMH - May 1970. (Box-folder 9-340)
- Hahn, T. Marshall - April. (Box-folder 9-341)
- Hahn, T. Marshall - March. (Box-folder 9-342)
- Hahn, T. Marshall - February. (Box-folder 9-343)
- Hahn, T. Marshall - January. (Box-folder 9-344)
- Harper, Laura Jane. (Box-folder 9-345)
- Health and Physical Education. (Box-folder 9-346)
- HEW Compliance Visit. (Box-folder 9-347)
- Heath, Education, Welfare. (Box-folder 9-348)
- HEEA - Correspondence. (Box-folder 9-349)
- WJM 70 - Higher Education. (Box-folder 9-350)
- WJM - Honor Court. (Box-folder 9-351)
- WJM - 70 Honors Seminar. (Box-folder 9-352)
- WJM - 70 Housing. (Box-folder 9-353)
- International Studies Program, 1969-1970. (Box-folder 9-354)
- TMH - Items for Discussion. (Box-folder 9-355)
- Information Services. (Box-folder 9-356)
- Institutional Research 1. (Box-folder 9-357)
- Institutional Research 2. (Box-folder 9-358)
- Intern Program. (Box-folder 10-359)
- Lavery, William E. 1. (Box-folder 10-360)
- Lavery, William E. 2. (Box-folder 10-361)
- International Programs. (Box-folder 10-362)
- Library Committee. (Box-folder 10-363)
- Living-Learning Committee. (Box-folder 10-364)
- Living-Learning Committee. (Box-folder 10-365)
- Malpass, Leslie F. 1. (Box-folder 10-366)
- Malpass, Leslie F. 2. (Box-folder 10-367)
- Mayor Washington Youth Program. (Box-folder 10-368)
- Mellon Foundation. (Box-folder 10-369)
- McKeefery - Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 10-370)
- McKeefery - Personal 1 of 2. (Box-folder 10-371)
- McKeefery - Personal 2 of 2. (Box-folder 10-372)
- Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 10-373)
- Mitchell, H.H. (Box-folder 10-374)
- Music. (Box-folder 10-375)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 10-376)
- National Association State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC). (Box-folder 10-377)
- Orientation. (Box-folder 10-378)
- Payne, Alfred C. (Box-folder 10-379)
- Personnel. (Box-folder 10-380)
- Philippines Trip. (Box-folder 10-381)
- Physics Department. (Box-folder 10-382)
- Placement. (Box-folder 10-383)
- Political Science. (Box-folder 10-384)
- Promotions - Faculty. (Box-folder 11-385)
- Radiation - Safety Committee. (Box-folder 11-386)
- Radio Club. (Box-folder 11-387)
- Research Division 1. (Box-folder 11-388)
- Research Division 2. (Box-folder 11-389)
- ROTC. (Box-folder 11-390)
- Ryland, Walter H. (Box-folder 11-391)
- Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities. (Box-folder 11-392)
- Southern Regional Education Board. (Box-folder 11-393)
- SREB Conference at Hilton Head. (Box-folder 11-394)
- Space Allocations. (Box-folder 11-395)
- Speech Ideas. (Box-folder 11-396)
- Speaking Engagements. (Box-folder 11-397)
- Staff Meeting 1 of 2. (Box-folder 11-398)
- Staff Meeting 2 of 2. (Box-folder 11-399)
- Staff Meeting #1, June 1969 - December 1970. (Box-folder 11-400)
- Staff Meeting #2, June 1969 - December 1970. (Box-folder 11-401)
- State Council of Higher Education. (Box-folder 11-402)
- Statements. (Box-folder 11-403)
- State Technical Services. (Box-folder 11-404)
- Statements. (Box-folder 11-405)
- Students. (Box-folder 11-406)
- Statistics Department. (Box-folder 11-407)
- Students - Review Cases. (Box-folder 11-408)
- Students - Disciplinary Probation. (Box-folder 11-409)
- Student Appeals - Academic. (Box-folder 11-410)
- Appeal Case - George E. Clark. (Box-folder 11-411)
- Students Traffic Violations. (Box-folder 11-412)
- Salaries. (Box-folder 11-413)
- Student Forums Board. (Box-folder 11-414)
- Student Health Service. (Box-folder 11-415)
- SGA Senate - Minutes. (Box-folder 11-416)
- Student Government/ (Box-folder 11-417)
- Student Union. (Box-folder 11-418)
- Study Abroad. (Box-folder 11-419)
- Summer School. (Box-folder 11-420)
- Systems Designs Meetings. (Box-folder 11-421)
- Tech Festival. (Box-folder 11-422)
- Theater Arts. (Box-folder 11-423)
- Traffic Committee. (Box-folder 11-424)
- Travel Authorizations for Out-of-State. (Box-folder 11-425)
- Transportation Planning. (Box-folder 11-426)
- TUMS. (Box-folder 11-427)
- University Council #3, Minutes And Agenda - 1, January - December 1970. (Box-folder 11-428)
- University Council #3 Minutes and Agenda - 2, January - December 1970. (Box-folder 11-429)
- University Council. (Box-folder 11-430)
- University Council. (Box-folder 11-431)
- University Enterprises. (Box-folder 11-432)
- University Council 1. (Box-folder 11-433)
- University Council 2. (Box-folder 12-434)
- Vice President Meetings. (Box-folder 12-435)
- Visiting Scholar Programs. (Box-folder 12-436)
- Washington Center for Metropolitan Centers. (Box-folder 12-437)
- Westinghouse. (Box-folder 12-438)
- Proposals 1. (Box-folder 12-439)
- Proposals 2. (Box-folder 12-440)
- Proposals 3. (Box-folder 12-441)
- Proposals 4. (Box-folder 12-442)
- Appeals. (Box-folder 12-443)
- Williams Lockin Letters. (Box-folder 12-444)
- Williams Hall Letters. (Box-folder 12-445)
- Williams Lockin Letters 3. (Box-folder 12-446)
- Drillfield, April 14, 1970. (Box-folder 12-447)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases A-C File 1 of 2. (Box-folder 12-448)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases A-C File 2 of 2. (Box-folder 12-449)